<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Jax Comedy</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="main_banner">main banner</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="now_hiring">Now Hiring!</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World!</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">Comedy doesn\'t have to be ugly!</string>
    <string name="about_the_club">The Comedy Club of Jacksonville opened in November 2012. Focused on great service,
        delicious food, and first rate ADULT comedy WITHOUT much of the vulgarity, we are excited to offer a higher level
        of entertainment. Our comics appear on David Letterman, Jay Leno, and Comedy Central and provide a night club act
        without the fatiguing repetition of hardcore language and content. Get a Jerry Seinfeld style of show, not Jerry
        Springer. We want your genuine belly laugh, not the embarrassing "what did that person just say" shock laughter
        that is associated with a foul comic.\n\nNot just sometimes, but each week our Friday and Saturday shows will be rated
        on two levels: CONTENT and LANGUAGE. Language is a \"soft R\" with no F-bombs, and Content is an \"R\" with adult humor
        but no hardcore vulgarity or language.\n\n We  anniversaries, or just a fun night out. And since most of our comics have
        never performed live in Jacksonville before, we offer a refreshing variety of top national touring comics who will give you
        lots of belly laughs.</string>
    <string name="more_room">The Comedy Club of Jacksonville seats 300 comfortably. Our tables are bigger (because we serve great
        food) and tables are spaced with more square footage per person, unlike the cramped seating of most other comedy clubs.
        No longer do you have to sit on the lap of the person you are seated next to, but stretch out and enjoy top national
        touring artists at the Comedy Club of Jacksonville.</string>
    <string name="best_seats">Check out The Best Seats in the House. For that special occasion or just a fun night out, The Best Seats
        in the House are actual front bucket seats from a 2007 XJ8 Jaguar automobile. They are functional for a custom seat position
        plus includes your first beverage.</string>
    <string name="no_two_item_minimum">Buy a ticket and that\'s it; we do have a full kitchen with high quality food and full bar plus
        we have great prices on our items, but will not force you to buy anything as other clubs do. Our service is fast and
        convenient and we hope you indulge but feel free to sit back and enjoy the show!</string>
    <string name="online_tickets">We are also happy that buying your ticket online costs the same as buying a ticket at the door. There
        is NO service charge for buying online. It is a free service, unlike other clubs who charge a few extra dollars to buy online.</string>
    <string name="app_exclusives">Similar to buying tickets online, reserving seats through our app costs the same as buying a ticket at
        the door.  Additionally, you have access to EXCLUSIVE deals only available to those download the app, as well as regular
        updates on our weekend shows.</string>
    <string name="saving_lives">The Comedy Club of Jacksonville is excited to work with The Blood Alliance in Jacksonville. In conjunction
        with The Blood Alliance, donors from Jacksonville companies who participate in a blood drive and exceed their goal earn a
        pair of tickets to a great night of comedy. Companies are recognized during the show with a stage shout out and a \"Thank
        You\" slide on our pre-show projector slide show. It is proven that laughter can extend your life, and by donating
        blood and sharing a laugh with us you get a double shot of \"Feel Good\".</string>
    <string name="directions_string">We are located at:\n11000 Beach Blvd\nJacksonville, FL 32246</string>
    <string name="name_text_view">Name:</string>
    <string name="message_text_view">Message:</string>
    <string name="name_edittext_hint">Enter name</string>
    <string name="message_edittext_hint">Enter message</string>
    <string name="send_email_button">Send Email</string>
    <string name="contact_textview_main">To speak with a human being or to leave a message, you may reach us by telephone. Our phone
        number is (904) 646-4277.\n\nAlternately, you may send an email by completing the fields below.\n</string>
    <string name="enter_text_hint">Enter text</string>
    <string name="nowhiring_main">We\'re always hiring at the Comedy Club of Jacksonville!\n\nTo apply, please email us your
        resume at info@jacksonvillecomedy.com.</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_textview_main">Any time is a great time to get your group, company, or friends together for some
		laughs.  We strive to offer top national touring comics who are not overly offensive or who have embarrassing humor, but
        who are able to perform comedy that is \"F\" bomb free.  Ask about our FREE Sample the Club offer!\n\nIf your party needs to be
        funny, clean, and delicious, press \'Reserve Seats\' below to begin your reservation, or you may request more information by
        clicking \'More Info\'.</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_button_reserve_seats">Reserve Seats</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_textview_date">Date:</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_edittext_enter_number">Enter number</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_textview_guests">Guests:</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_textview_reservation_name">Reservation/Company Name:</string>
    <string name="groupsandparties_button_more_info">More Info</string>
    <string name="reserve_textview_show_time">Pick a show time:</string>
    <string name="reserve_radiobutton_804_show">8:04 show (soft-R)</string>
    <string name="reserve_radiobutton_1010_showtime">10:10 show (uncut)</string>
    <string name="reserve_radiobutton_other_show">Other (special event)</string>
    <string name="textview_deals_points_title">Reward Points:</string>
    <string name="textview_deals_rewards_info">Earn 5 points per ticket purchase and 2 each week for viewing notifications.  To claim
        points from ticket purchases or to redeem points, present your device to the host when you arrive.</string>
    <string name="textview_redeem_confirm_password">Password:</string>
    <string name="textview_redeem_enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="button_redeem">Redeem</string>
    <string name="button_add_points">Add points</string>
    <string name="textview_enter_email">Email Address:</string>
    <string name="edittext_hint_enter_email">Enter email</string>
    <string name="tv_calendar_information">Select any show below to view information about the comedian. Click on the comedian\'s
        information to reserve seats for any available showtimes.</string>
    <string name="report_a_bug">Report a Bug</string>
    <string name="textview_report_bug_main">I\'m sorry something doesn\'t work; I\'m only human after all! To best help me fix any
        errors you\'re encountering, fill out the fields below. Be as descriptive as possible, and include details such as where the
        error occurred and what device you\'re using.\n</string>
    <string name="enter_steps">Enter steps</string>
    <string name="textview_report_bug_steps">Please list the steps to recreate:</string>
    <string name="enter_description">Enter description</string>
    <string name="textview_report_bug_describe">Describe the error:</string>
    <string name="submit_bug_report">Submit Bug Report</string>
    <string name="textview_this_weekend_header">Headlining this weekend at the Comedy Club of Jacksonville:</string>
    <string name="reserve_seats">Reserve Seats</string>
    <string name="appetizers">Stuffed Jalapeno Poppers\nFried Onion Rings\nMozzarella Sticks\nTortilla Chips with Salsa\nFrench Fries
        \nPotato Skins with Cheese and Bacon</string>
    <string name="salads">Regular Tossed and Caesar Salads, optionally served with\n\tFilet Mignon\n\tGrilled Chicken\n\tCrispy Chicken</string>
    <string name="shtick_entrees">Seasoned Filet Mignon Tips\nSeasoned Grilled Chicken</string>
    <string name="additional">Wings(8) Mild/Hot\nChicken Tenders\nCoconut Fried Shrimp (6) with Orange Marmalade\nTacos (shredded beef or chicken)</string>
    <string name="bun_entrees">Laurel &amp; Hearty Burger\nPhilly Cheese Burger with Onions and Peppers\nSmokehouse Burger\nComedy Club \"Club\" Sandwich\n
        Crispy Fried Chicken Sandwich\nGrilled Chicken Breast Sandwich\nBLT\nAll Beef Hot Dog (1/4 lb)</string>
    <string name="pizza">8\" Personal (cheese, pepperoni, or sausage)\n12\" Large (cheese, pepperoni, or sausage)</string>
    <string name="cakes">Fresh cakes straight from the Beaches.  Varies by availability.\n\t\tChocoholic\n\t\tOld Yeller\n\t\tCarrot\n
        \t\tRed Velvet\n\t\tStrawberry Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="beer">Budweiser\nBud Light\nBud Light Lime\nCoors Light\nMiller Light\nMichelob Ultra\nCorona\nYuengling\nBlue Moon</string>
    <string name="wine">Chardonnay\nMoscato\nPinot Grigio\nRiesling\nWhite Zinfandel\nCabernet\nMerlot</string>
    <string name="vodka">Grey Goose\n3 Olives, 3 Olives Flavors\nMartinis</string>
    <string name="rum">Bacardi, Bacardi Limon\nMalibu\nSailor Jerry\'s Spiced\nMyer\'s</string>
    <string name="gin">Tangueray</string>
    <string name="tequila">Jose Quervo Gold\nPatron Silver</string>
    <string name="scotch">Dewar\'s\nJohnny Walker Red</string>
    <string name="bourbons_blends_whiskeys">Jack Daniel\'s\nSo Co\nJim Beam\nSeagrams 7\nCrown Royal\nJameson\nMaker\'s Mark</string>
    <string name="cordials_liqueurs">Amaretto, Amaretto Di Saronno\nRazz Ma Tazz\nBrandy\nMidori\nSloe Gin\nGrand Marnier\nJager\nBailey\'s\nKahlua</string>
    <string name="non_alcoholic">Coke, Diet Coke\nSprite\nGinger Ale\nSweet/Unsweet Tea\nCoffee\nBottled Water\nRed Bull\nJodi Juice with Sugar Rim</string>
    <string name="drink_menu">Drink Menu</string>
    <string name="food_menu">Food Menu</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="reserve_checkbox_request_best_seats">Request Best Seats</string>
    <string name="tap_to_reserve">(Tap to reserve)</string>
    <string name="tap_to_redeem">(Tap to redeem)</string>

</resources>
